Guide to the Time Inc. Corporate Public Affairs Department Records 1945-2000 (bulk 1959-1996) MS 3009-RG 19
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Vice President Donald Wilson Files, 1960-1994; 1968-1989; 218328; 62.5 Linear feet (63 boxes)
  - New York City: Regional Plan Association: Citizens Mobilization Board, 1975-1976; 219483 (Offsite-box 1666, Folder 19)
  - Newspaper Guild: General, 1986-1988; 219484 (Offsite-box 1666, Folder 20-21)
    Includes issues of the newsletter On Time.
  - Newspaper Guild: Strike, 1976; 229017 (Offsite-box 1957, Folder 6-7)
  - Newspaper Subscriptions, 1987; 219485 (Offsite-box 1666, Folder 22)
  - Newstours: Middle East, 1975; 219486 (Offsite-box 1666, Folder 23-24)
  - Newstours: Africa/Middle East, 1978; 219487 (Offsite-box 1667, Folder 1-5)
  - Newstours: Mexico, 1979; 219488 (Offsite-box 1667, Folder 6)
  - Newstours: 1981 (Eastern Europe, Russia, Middle East), 219489 (Offsite-box 1667, Folder 7-9)
  - Newstours: Mexico, 1983; 219490 (Offsite-box 1667, Folder 10)
  - Newstours: Pacific Rim, 1985; 219491 (Offsite-box 1667, Folder 11-14)
  - Newstours: Pacific Rim, 1985; 219493 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 1-6)
  - Newstours: USSR (Soviet Union), 1987-1988; 219494 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 7)
  - New York Festival, 1981; 219495 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 8)
  - New York Perspectives Meetings, 1977-1979; 219497 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 9-11)
  - New York Public Library, 1979-1983; 219498 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 12)
  - New York State Bonus Tax Bill, 1978; 219499 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 13)
  - Nicholas, N. J.: Breakfast Meetings, 1988; 219501 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 14)
  - Non-Executive Briefing Lunches, 1985; 219502 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 15)
  - Non-Financial Goals Determined by Munro, 1981-1983; 219503 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 16)
  - Nuclear Weapons and Atlantic Alliance, 1982; 219504 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 17)
  - Office Relocation of Wilson, 1987; 219506 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 18)
  - Overseas Development Council, 1982; 219507 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 19)
  - Olympics, 1984; 219508 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 20)
  - Paddle Tennis Courts, 1976; 219510 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 21)
  - Parenting, 1986; 219511 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 22)
  - Patterson, Martha Priddy: Correspondence on Tax Legislation, 1986; 219512 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 23-25)
  - People, 1979-1988; 219513 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 26)
  - Personnel: General, 1981-1986; 219514 (Offsite-box 1668, Folder 27-29)
  - Personnel: General, 1986-1988; 219525 (Offsite-box 1669, Folder 1)
  - Personnel: Anderson, Lem [RESTRICTED], 1977-1984; 219908 (Offsite-box R25)
  - Personnel: Campbell, Ron [RESTRICTED], 1984-1987; 219909 (Offsite-box R25)
  - Personnel: Employee Benefits, 1986; 219526 (Offsite-box 1669, Folder 2)
  - Personnel: Employee Opinion Survey Results, 1984-1985; 219527 (Offsite-box 1669, Folder 3)
  - Personnel: Expense Account Privileges and Authorization Forms, 1986; 219528 (Offsite-box 1669, Folder 4)
  - Personnel: Kapner, Stan [RESTRICTED], 1979-1986; 219910 (Offsite-box R25)
  - Personnel: Kerr, Jeanne, 1984-1987; 219530 (Offsite-box 1669, Folder 5-6)
  - Personnel: Kerr, Jeanne [RESTRICTED], 219911 (Offsite-box R25)
  - Personnel: Monthly Overtime Reports, 1986; 219531 (Offsite-box 1669, Folder 7)
  - Personnel: Morfogen, Zach [RESTRICTED], 1978-1988; 219912 (Offsite-box R25)
  - Personnel: Public Affairs [RESTRICTED], 1988; 219913 (Offsite-box R25)
  - Personnel: Public Relations, 1969-1985; 219532 (Offsite-box 1669, Folder 8-21)
  - Personnel: Public Relations, 1986; 219533 (Offsite-box 1670, Folder 1-2)
  - Personnel: Public Relations [RESTRICTED], 219914 (Offsite-box R25)
  - Personnel: Public Relations [RESTRICTED], 219962 (Offsite-box R26)
  - Personnel: Quinn, Peter, 1985-1988; 219534 (Offsite-box 1670, Folder 3-4)
  - Personnel: Rowan, Roy [RESTRICTED], 1985-1986; 219963 (Offsite-box R26)
  - Personnel: Search Firms, 1982; 219535 (Offsite-box 1670, Folder 5)
  - Personnel: Speechwriter, 1985; 219536 (Offsite-box 1670, Folder 6)
  - Personnel: Staff Evaluations, 1976-1986; 219537 (Offsite-box 1670, Folder 7)
  - Personnel: Steele, John [RESTRICTED], 1982-1983; 219964 (Offsite-box R26)
  - Personnel: Summer Intern Program, 1985; 219538 (Offsite-box 1670, Folder 8)
  - Personnel: Zorthian, Barry, 1979; 219539 (Offsite-box 1670, Folder 9)
  - Physical Fitness Program, 1976-1977; 219540 (Offsite-box 1670, Folder 10)
  - Picture Collection, 1981-1988; 219541 (Offsite-box 1670, Folder 11)
  - Picture Week: General, 1985-1986; 219542 (Offsite-box 1670, Folder 12)
  - Picture Week: Shutdown, 1986; 219543 (Offsite-box 1670, Folder 13)
  - Picture Week: Shutdown [RESTRICTED], 219965 (Offsite-box R26)
  - Political Action Committee: Clips, 1982; 219544 (Offsite-box 1670, Folder 14)
  - Political Action Committee: Committee for Good Government, 1978-1979; 219545 (Offsite-box 1670, Folder 15-17)
  - Political Action Committee: Committee for Good Government, 1979-1980; 219546 (Offsite-box 1671, Folder 1-6)
  - Political Action Committee: Inland Container Corporation, 1978-1983; 219547 (Offsite-box 1671, Folder 7)
  - Political Action Committee: Koch, Ed, 1980-1981; 219548 (Offsite-box 1671, Folder 8-9)
  - Political Action Committee of Time Inc., 1981; 219549 (Offsite-box 1671, Folder 10-13)
  - Political Action Committee of Time Inc., 1982; 219550 (Offsite-box 1672, Folder 1-6)
  - Political Action Committee: Temple-Eastex, 1981-1982; 219551 (Offsite-box 1672, Folder 7)
  - Political Action Committees, 1976-1983; 219552 (Offsite-box 1672, Folder 8-10)
  - Political Action Committees [RESTRICTED], 219966 (Offsite-box R26)
  - Political Contributions: State, 1976-1981; 219553 (Offsite-box 1672, Folder 11)
  - Political Conventions, 1988; 219554 (Offsite-box 1672, Folder 12)
  - Portrait: Donovan, Hedley, 1979-1980; 219555 (Offsite-box 1672, Folder 13)
  - Portrait: Heiskell, Andrew, undated; 219556 (Offsite-box 1672, Folder 14)
  - Portrait: Larsen, Roy, 1979; 219557 (Offsite-box 1672, Folder 15)
  - Postal, 1982-1987; 219558 (Offsite-box 1672, Folder 16-18)
  - Postal: Coalition, 1976; 219621 (Offsite-box 1673, Folder 1)
  - Postal: Correspondence: President Ford Letter, 1975-1978; 219622 (Offsite-box 1673, Folder 2-3)
  - Postal: National Newspaper Association, 1975-1976; 219623 (Offsite-box 1673, Folder 4)
  - Postal: Responses to Heiskell President Ford Letter, 1976; 219624 (Offsite-box 1673, Folder 5-7)
  - Presentation: American Television and Communications Corporation (ATC), 1979; 219627 (Offsite-box 1673, Folder 8)
  - Presentation: Book-of-the-Month Club, 1979; 219628 (Offsite-box 1673, Folder 9)
  - Presentation: Film on Women's Magazine, 1976-1978; 219630 (Offsite-box 1673, Folder 10)
  - Presentation: Home Box Office (HBO), 1978; 219631 (Offsite-box 1673, Folder 11)
  - Presentation: Inland Container Corporation, 1979; 219632 (Offsite-box 1673, Folder 12)
  - Presentation: Washington Star, 1978; 219634 (Offsite-box 1673, Folder 13)
  - Presentation on Time Inc., 1978; 219635 (Offsite-box 1673, Folder 14)
  - Presidential Conventions, 1983-1984; 219636 (Offsite-box 1673, Folder 15)
  - Presidential Inauguration, 1984-1985; 219638 (Offsite-box 1673, Folder 16)
  - Press Releases: General, 1984-1987; 219639 (Offsite-box 1673, Folder 17-19)
  - Press Releases: General, 1986-1988; 219641 (Offsite-box 1674, Folder 1-3)
  - Press Releases: Earnings, 1969-1988; 219642 (Offsite-box 1674, Folder 4-7)
  - Press Releases and Shareholder Reports, 1987; 219643 (Offsite-box 1674, Folder 8)
  - Privacy Protection Study Commission, 1975; 219644 (Offsite-box 1674, Folder 9)
  - Prizes, 1972-1988; 219645 (Offsite-box 1674, Folder 10-11)
  - Prizes: Awards, 1969-1981; 219646 (Offsite-box 1674, Folder 12-14)
  - Prizes: Heiskell Awards, 1981-1988; 219647 (Offsite-box 1675, Folder 1-5)
  - Prizes: National Magazine Awards, 1973-1989; 219648 (Offsite-box 1675, Folder 6-7)
  - Profit-Sharing Memorandum [RESTRICTED], 1985-1987; 219967 (Offsite-box R26)
  - Prospectus on $50 Million Note, 1986; 219649 (Offsite-box 1675, Folder 8)
  - Public Affairs: Conferences, 1982-1985; 219650 (Offsite-box 1675, Folder 9-13)
  - Public Affairs: Mission Statement, 1986; 219651 (Offsite-box 1675, Folder 14)
  - Public Affairs: Releasing Time Inc. News in Press Releases, 1986; 219652 (Offsite-box 1675, Folder 15)
  - Public Affairs: Space Requirements, 1981-1987; 219653 (Offsite-box 1675, Folder 16)
  - Public Relations Department, 1985-1987; 219655 (Offsite-box 1676, Folder 1)
  - Public Relations: Meetings, 1976-1988; 219657 (Offsite-box 1676, Folder 2)
  - Public Relations: Seminars, 1981-1987; 219658 (Offsite-box 1676, Folder 3-10)
  - Questionnaires and Surveys from Other Organizations, 1983-1989; 219659 (Offsite-box 1676, Folder 11-13)
  - Rackleff Farewell Party, 1985; 219660 (Offsite-box 1676, Folder 14)
  - Radio/TV Publicity Department, 1984-1988; 219677 (Offsite-box 1676, Folder 15)
  - Reading Habits Report, 1974-1976; 219678 (Offsite-box 1676, Folder 16)
  - Restaurants: Private Rooms, undated; 219679 (Offsite-box 1676, Folder 17)
  - Retirement Party: Shepley, James, 1982; 219681 (Offsite-box 1676, Folder 18)
  - Right to Privacy Act, 1974-1975; 219682 (Offsite-box 1676, Folder 19)
  - Role of the Editor-in-Chief, 1986; 219684 (Offsite-box 1676, Folder 20)
  - Sackler, Arthur: Correspondence on Postal Issues, 1986-1988; 219686 (Offsite-box 1676, Folder 21-22)
  - Sackler, Arthur: Correspondence on Postal Issues [RESTRICTED], 219968 (Offsite-box R26)
  - Savings Bond Campaign, 1986-1987; 219687 (Offsite-box 1676, Folder 23)
  - Science 86, 1986; 219688 (Offsite-box 1676, Folder 24)
  - Security Analysts Meeting, 1984; 219689 (Offsite-box 1676, Folder 25)
  - Selling Areas-Marketing, Inc. (SAMI), 1985-1987; 219726 (Offsite-box 1677, Folder 1-2)
  - Shepley, James: Memoria Service, 1988; 219727 (Offsite-box 1677, Folder 3)
  - Slovinsky, Louis: Memoranda and Speeches, 1970-1988; 219730 (Offsite-box 1677, Folder 4-9)
  - Small, Anita: Postal Management, 1985; 219732 (Offsite-box 1677, Folder 10)
  - Southern Progress Corporation, 1985-1988; 219733 (Offsite-box 1677, Folder 11-14)
  - Space Reallocation Plan: 34th Floor, 1987; 219736 (Offsite-box 1677, Folder 15)
  - Special Stockholders Meeting, 1977; 219737 (Offsite-box 1677, Folder 16)
  - Speech Assignments, 1981-1983; 219738 (Offsite-box 1677, Folder 17)
    Includes schedules of executive speeches.
  - Speech Material, 1965-1974; 219739 (Offsite-box 1677, Folder 18)
  - Speeches: General, 1985-1988; 219740 (Offsite-box 1677, Folder 19-20)
  - Speeches About Time Inc. by Munro and Levin, 1984; 219744 (Offsite-box 1678, Folder 1)
  - Speeches: Banks, Louis, 1972; 219745 (Offsite-box 1678, Folder 2)
  - Speeches: Brack, Reginald, 1988; 219746 (Offsite-box 1678, Folder 3)
  - Speeches: Davidson, Ralph, 1982-1986; 219747 (Offsite-box 1678, Folder 4-7)
  - Speeches: Donovan, Hedley, 1972-1973; 219748 (Offsite-box 1678, Folder 8)
  - Speeches: Grunwald, Henry, 1972-1973; 219749 (Offsite-box 1678, Folder 9)
  - Speeches: McManus, Jason, 1988; 219750 (Offsite-box 1678, Folder 10)
  - Speeches: Munro, J. Richard, 1981-1988; 219753 (Offsite-box 1678, Folder 11-17)
  - Speeches: Nicholas, N. J., 1987-1988; 219755 (Offsite-box 1679, Folder 1-2)
  - Speeches: Potential Speech Audiences: Rackleff Memoranda, 1981; 219757 (Offsite-box 1679, Folder 3)
  - Speeches: Wilson, Donald, 1962-1970; 219759 (Offsite-box 1679, Folder 4-5)
  - Sports Illustrated, 1984-1988; 219760 (Offsite-box 1679, Folder 6)
  - Sports Illustrated: Ludtke, Melissa [RESTRICTED], 1979; 219969 (Offsite-box R26)
  - Sports Illustrated For Kids: Corporate Ad Campaign, 1988; 219762 (Offsite-box 1679, Folder 7)
  - Staff Announcement: Brack and Carl Jaeger Exchanging Jobs, 1982; 219764 (Offsite-box 1679, Folder 8)
  - Staff: Dissent, 1970; 219765 (Offsite-box 1679, Folder 9)
  - Staff Presentations, 1975-1982; 219766 (Offsite-box 1679, Folder 10-12)
  - Steele, John: Luncheon, 1982; 219774 (Offsite-box 1679, Folder 13)
  - Stock Option Group, 1972-1973; 219775 (Offsite-box 1679, Folder 14)
  - Stock Plan Recommendation Schedule, 1986; 219776 (Offsite-box 1679, Folder 15)
  - Stockholder Proposal Meeting, 1987-1988; 219778 (Offsite-box 1679, Folder 16)
  - Stockholders Letter, 1976-1988; 219779 (Offsite-box 1679, Folder 17-20)
    Includes Shareholder Reports.
  - Stockholders Meetings, 1978-1983; 219781 (Offsite-box 1680, Folder 1-3)
  - Stolley, Richard: Announcement of New position as Director of Special Projects, 1987; 219783 (Offsite-box 1680, Folder 4)
  - St. Regis Paper Strike, 1979; 219784 (Offsite-box 1680, Folder 5)
  - Subscriptions to Newsletters and Newspapers, 1987-1988; 219786 (Offsite-box 1680, Folder 6)
  - Successor in ___ Corp: Out Card, undated; 219787 (Offsite-box 1680, Folder 7)
  - Task Force Review Meeting, 1976-1977; 219788 (Offsite-box 1680, Folder 8)
  - TBS Negotiations: Turner Broadcast, 1987; 219789 (Offsite-box 1680, Folder 9)
  - Teletext, 1982-1983; 219790 (Offsite-box 1680, Folder 10)
  - Temple-Eastex, 1971-1981; 219816 (Offsite-box 1680, Folder 11-13)
  - Temple-Eastex [RESTRICTED], 219974 (Offsite-box R26)
  - Temple Family Stock, 1979; 219817 (Offsite-box 1680, Folder 14)
  - Tennis Tournament: Corporate v. Home Box Office (HBO), 1983; 219818 (Offsite-box 1680, Folder 15)
  - Third World Countries and Western Press, 1976-1983; 219819 (Offsite-box 1680, Folder 16-18)
  - Third World: International Press Institute: World Press Freedom Committee, 1980-1981; 219820 (Offsite-box 1680, Folder 19)
  - Third World and Press Freedom: The Murrow Center Conference, 1977; 219821 (Offsite-box 1680, Folder 20-21)
  - Third World and Press Freedom: The Murrow Center Conference, 1977; 219822 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 1)
  - Time Canada Ltd., 1978-1986; 219823 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 2)
  - Time Distribution Services, 1978; 219824 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 3)
  - Time U.S. Sales Conference, 1982; 219825 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 4)
  - Time Inc. Academic Award Program, 1984-1987; 219826 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 5)
  - Time Inc. History: Volume III, 1984-1986; 219827 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 6-8)
  - Time Inc. in Profile, undated; 219828 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 9)
  - Time Inc. Presentation: "The Best is Yet to Come", 1984; 219791 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 10)
  - Time Inc. Public Affairs Conference, 1986-1987; 219792 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 11)
  - Time Inc. Scholars, 1983-1985; 219793 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 12)
  - Time Inc. Volunteer Fund, 1976-1987; 219794 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 13)
  - Time Inc. Volunteer Program, 1985; 219795 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 14)
  - Time Inc. Volunteer Retirees Program, 1983-1986; 219796 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 15)
  - Time-Life Alumni Society, 1984-1988; 219797 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 16)
  - Time-Life Books, 1980-1988; 219798 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 17)
  - Time-Life Books and Records, 1982; 219799 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 18)
  - Time-Life Films and 20th Century Fox Merger, 1981; 219800 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 19)
  - Time-Life Video, 1981-1985; 219801 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 20)
  - Time-Life Video [RESTRICTED], 219975 (Offsite-box R26)
  - Time: General, 1983-1988; 219802 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 21-22)
  - Time and the Central Intelligence Agency (CIA) on Chile, 1978; 219803 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 23)
  - Time: Lance, Bert, 1977; 219804 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 24)
  - Time: Military Mini-Newstour, 1986; 219805 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 25)
  - Time: 60th Anniversary: Distinguished Speakers Program, 1984-1987; 219806 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 26)
  - Tobacco Advertising, 1982; 219807 (Offsite-box 1681, Folder 27)
  - Tort Policy Task Force, 1986; 219829 (Offsite-box 1682, Folder 1-2)
  - Transfer, Pricing, and Controlling Reports, 1978-1981; 229018 (Offsite-box 1957, Folder 8-9)
  - Trips: American Television and Communications Corporation Conference: Denver, CO, 1983; 219830 (Offsite-box 1682, Folder 3)
  - Trips: Board of Directors: Birmingham, AL, 1985; 219831 (Offsite-box 1682, Folder 4)
  - Trips: Boston: MIT Dedication Ceremonies Arts and Media Technology Building, 1985; 219832 (Offsite-box 1682, Folder 5)
  - Trips: Charleston: Time to Read, 1987; 219833 (Offsite-box 1682, Folder 6)
  - Trips: Chicago: 60th Anniversary, 1985; 219834 (Offsite-box 1682, Folder 7)
  - Trips: Citizens Research Foundation Honoring Theodore White: Washington, D.C., 1988; 219835 (Offsite-box 1682, Folder 8)
  - Trips: Fortune Corporate Communications Conference: Tuscon, AZ, 1986; 219836 (Offsite-box 1682, Folder 9)
  - Trips: International Industrial Conference, 1985; 219837 (Offsite-box 1682, Folder 10-11)
  - Trips: Kapner, Stan: Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1985; 219838 (Offsite-box 1682, Folder 12)
  - Trips: Lyford Cay, 1988; 219839 (Offsite-box 1682, Folder 13)
  - Trips: Time to Read Literacy Conference: Jacksonville, FL, 1988; 219840 (Offsite-box 1682, Folder 14)
  - Trips: Tufts University, 1986; 219841 (Offsite-box 1682, Folder 15)
  - Trips: Washington, D.C.: The Business Roundtable, 1986; 219842 (Offsite-box 1682, Folder 16)
  - Trips: Wyandanch, 1985; 219843 (Offsite-box 1683, Folder 1)
  - TV-Cable Week, 1982-1983; 229019 (Offsite-box 1957, Folder 10-11)
  - Uebelhoer, Urban "Pete": Retirement, 1986; 219844 (Offsite-box 1683, Folder 2)
  - United Fund, 1972-1977; 219845 (Offsite-box 1683, Folder 3-11)
  - United Negro College Fund, 1980-1982; 219846 (Offsite-box 1683, Folder 12)
  - United States Information Agency (USIA), 1965-1982; 219847 (Offsite-box 1683, Folder 13)
  - United Way: General, 1978-1980; 219848 (Offsite-box 1683, Folder 14-16)
  - United Way: General, 1980-1985; 219849 (Offsite-box 1684)
  - United Way: General, 1985-1988; 219850 (Offsite-box 1685, Folder 1-9)
  - United Way: Clips, 1979-1982; 219851 (Offsite-box 1685, Folder 10)
  - United Way: Employee and Corporate Giving History, 1987; 219852 (Offsite-box 1685, Folder 11)
  - United Way: List of Chairmen, undated; 219853 (Offsite-box 1685, Folder 12)
  - United Way: Loaned Executive Program, 1987-1988; 219854 (Offsite-box 1685, Folder 13-14)
  - United Way: Munro, J. Richard, 1984; 219855 (Offsite-box 1685, Folder 15)
  - United Way: National Corporate Leadership Program, 1987; 219856 (Offsite-box 1685, Folder 16)
  - Valk, Lisa, 1986; 219857 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 1)
  - Video Group, 1984-1985; 219858 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 2)
  - Warner-Amex, 1985; 219859 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 3)
  - Warner Cable Corporation, 1980; 219860 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 4)
  - Warner Communications, 1987-1988; 219861 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 5)
  - Washington: Correspondence on Lease on Hotel, 1979; 219862 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 6)
  - Washington: Correspondence on Lease on Hotel [RESTRICTED], 219976 (Offsite-box R26)
  - Washington: Expenses, 1976-1988; 219863 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 7)
  - Washington: Hay Adams Lease, 1979-1981; 219864 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 8)
  - Washington: Hay Adams Lease [RESTRICTED], 219977 (Offsite-box R26)
  - Washington: Meeting on Forest Products, 1982; 219865 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 9)
  - Washington Office, 1982-1988; 219866 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 10)
  - Washington Star: General, 1978-1981; 223856 (Offsite-box 1857, Folder 8-9)
  - Washington Star: Acquisition, 1978; 223857 (Offsite-box 1857, Folder 10-11)
  - Washington Star: Demise, 1981; 219867 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 11)
  - Washington Star: Demise Press Clips, 1981; 223858 (Offsite-box 1857, Folder 12)
  - Washington Star: Letter from James Shepley to Harold McGraw, 1978-1979; 223859 (Offsite-box 1857, Folder 13)
  - Washington Star: Union Negotiations, 1978; 223860 (Offsite-box 1857, Folder 14-15)
  - Washington Suite, 1986-1987; 219868 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 12)
  - Watergate Apartment Lease, 1979-1980; 219869 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 13)
  - Watergate Apartment Lease [RESTRICTED], 219978 (Offsite-box R26)
  - Weekly Publishers Association, undated; 219870 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 14)
  - Whittingham, Charles: Retirement, 1986; 219871 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 15)
  - Whittle Communications, 1988; 219872 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 16)
  - Woman Magazine, 1977; 219873 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 17)
  - Women Executives at Time Inc., 1986; 219874 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 18)
  - Women's Activities, 1970-1975; 219876 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 19)
  - Word Processing Equipment, 1980-1981; 219877 (Offsite-box 1726, Folder 20)
- Series II. Associate Director Louis Slovinsky Chron Files, 1975-1978; 0.5 Linear feet (7 folders)
  Scope and Contents
  Slovinsky's chron files contain his incoming and outgoing correspondence while he was the public relations manager and associate director of public affairs.
  Arrangement
  Organized chronologically based on the original order.
  - Chron Files, 1975-1978; 218329 (Offsite-box 1749, Folder 1-7)
- Series III. Radio/TV Publicity Office Files, 1974-1990; 220697; 2.5 Linear feet (3 record cartons)
  Historical Note
  The first listing of the Radio/TV Publicity Office in the Department Head Lists in the Time Inc. Reference Files is in 1974. According to Robert Sweeney's files in Time Public Affairs, the office existed as early as 1964 with Lisa Fillman as the manager. Marilyn Sahner was the director from 1974 through her retirement in 1991. Katharine Trowbridge Carroll, then Patti Strauss were Assistant Directors.
  Citation:
  Time Inc. Reference Files, MS 3009-RG 3, New-York Historical Society.
  Records include radio and television appearance schedules for Time Inc. staff interviews; correspondence with show hosts and news directors to pitch possible topics and interviewees and to coordinate appearances; press releases; memoranda from the interviewees reporting on their interview experiences; booking sheets; and notes to file on reactions to the pitches and interviews. Frequent interviewees were corporate editorial staff; Time editorial staff, photojournalists, and correspondents; and magazine ad promotion directors.
  Organized alphabetically with arrangement imposed.
  - The Alexander Project, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 2506, Folder 6-7)
  - CBS RadioRadio, 1982-1984 (Offsite-box 2506, Folder 8)
  - Exhibition: Hollywood: Legend and Reality, 1985-1987 (Offsite-box 2506, Folder 9-11)
  - Life Gallery, 1983-1984 (Offsite-box 2506, Folder 12)
  - Time: General, 1989; 220703 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 1-2)
  - Time: American Express Party in Miami, 1989; 220704 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 3)
  - Time: Anniversary, 1983; 220705 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 4)
  - Time: Baby Buster Cover Story, 1990; 220706 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 5)
  - Time: Bicentennial, 1975-1976; 220707 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 6-8)
  - Time: Book on China, 1989; 220708 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 9)
  - Time: Book on Gorbachev, Mikhail, 1988; 220709 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 10-16)
  - Time: Book: The Winning of the White House, 1988; 220710 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 17)
  - Time: College Achievement Awards (out card), 1988; 220711 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 18)
  - Time: Creative Arts Series at New York University, 1989; 220712 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 19)
  - Time: Democratic Conventions, 1984-1988; 220714 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 20-21)
  - Time: Environmental Challenge, 1990; 220715 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 22)
  - Time: History of Photojournalism, 1989; 220716 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 23)
  - Time: Jackson, Dave, 1988-1989; 220717 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 24)
  - Time: Immigration Issue, 1985; 220718 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 25)
  - Time: Leadership Conference, 1976; 220719 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 26)
  - Time: Leadership Issue, 1974; 220720 (Offsite-box 1747, Folder 27)
  - Time: Man of the Year: 1982, 1982-1983; 220722 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 1)
  - Time: Man of the Year: 1984, 1984-1985; 220723 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 2)
  - Time: Man of the Year: 1986, 1985-1986; 220724 (Offsite-box 1748, Folder 3)